https://stocktoninfrared.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Stockton Infrared Thermographic Services, Inc. (SITS) values your privacy. Thank you for reviewing our privacy commitment to you.
Our privacy policy tells you about our information practices when you provide personal information to us, whether collected online or offline, and when you visit us online to browse, obtain information, or conduct a transaction. Stockton Infrared collects personal information from you in order to provide you with certain products and services, and if needed to respond to your inquiries or requests for information.
Personal information may include your name, email, mailing and/or business address, phone numbers, or other information that identifies you personally.
We do not sell or rent your personal information to outside parties.
We require that our service providers adhere to our privacy requirements.
We do not require you to register or provide personal information in order to visit our main web site.
We only use web analysis tools (e.g., cookies) for the limited purposes authorized in this policy.
Legal Notice
All materials contained herein are trademarked and copyrighted (1988-2012). All data, images or any other documentation is the exclusive property of Stockton Infrared Thermographic Services, Inc. (SITS). The name “AreaScanIR™,” and other trade names, trademarks, service marks, logos and other commercial symbols (collectively the “Marks”) are hereby protected. All content, images, systems, formats, designs, methods, specifications, standards, procedures, software or other technology, whether patented, licensed, or designated by SITS are and shall be the sole property of SITS. User shall have no right to use any of the Marks without the express written consent of SITS.
